SHRINIVAS SHIVANE

Gandhinagar 382421 ◆ **H:** 7203911651 ◆ **C:** 9879111651 ◆ sshrinivas@rediffmail.com

OBJECTIVE

To achieve challenging and rewarding career by utilizing more than 25 years of warehouse, Logistics, Commercial & Excise management experience with creativity and working abilities. Contributing to profitability, productivity and performance of the organization through human resources leadership & systems development.

SKILLS

- Manage entire Warehouse operations, contracts and performances of external Logistics Service providers (LSP) in order to optimize effectiveness of storage, line haul and transport.
- Software Development for the Dept. in SAP, & E.R.P.
- Monitoring & Maintaining all data & transactions in SAP & E.R.P.
- Implementation of SAP for proper Material Management (MM) planning & Control (PP) Sales & Distribution (SD).
- Providing Training for power user & end user for smooth running.
- Handled Commercial, Logistics, Warehouse & Excise functions.

- Confidentiality agreements
- Contract management
- Business planning and development
- Stress-Resistant, Team player, Self-starter, Able to perform under pressure and Possess versatile communication skills and proper language skills. (English, Hindi, Gujarati & Marathi)
- Quick learner and open to new experiences

WORK HISTORY

Warehouse Manager, 12/2014 - Current

Arvind Ltd - Ahmadabad

- Planning of 40 MT/Day greige fabrics issue for processing.
- Planning of 25 MT/Day yarn issue for knitting.
- Planning of 400 MT yarn dispatches for job work of greige fabrics.
- Meetings with the management for controlling of the aged fabrics & yarn
- To attend Production Planning meeting on daily basis and communicate to all the supervisors to meet the commitment.
- Maintaining Daily & Monthly stock.
- Develop and review periodically, all Standard Operating procedures (SOP) and ensure strict compliance's of ISO standards.

Commercial Manager, 05/2008 - 12/2014

Alok Industries Ltd – Silvassa

- Planning to Dispatch 1200 MT/Day of POY, 100 MT/Day CHIPS & 50 MT/Day of PSF and oversee execution of sales orders in order to maintain proper & highest levels dispatches.
- Set-up and monitor key performance indicators for effective Sales Order Planning, Execution, Distribution, Billing and maintain customer service standards.
- Communicate the pending sales orders product-wise to production department and prioritize.
- Maintaining Daily & Monthly stock.
- Warehouse & Warehousing Management.
- Materials planning and Procurement of Materials to meet the Production plan.
- Collection & accounting of returnable Pallets & material from parties.
- Continuously monitoring supplier performance ratings in terms of Quality, Cost & Delivery.
- Achieving target sales of POY, CHIPS, PSF & co-ordinates with Marketing Peoples.
- Establish smooth co-ordination with relevant departments and streamline the Delivery process.

Sr. Officer Warehouse, 08/2005 - 05/2008

Garden Silk Mills Ltd – Surat

Gujarati

- Maintaining Daily & Monthly stock.
- Warehouse & Warehousing Management.
- Materials planning and Procurement of Materials to meet the Production plan.

Head of Dept. of Dispatch & Excise, 03/2004 - 07/2005

Orange Polymers Ltd – Navapur

In Charge of Packing & Dispatch, 03/1998 - 02/2004

Sanjiv & Co – Surat, india

Assistant, 06/1997 - 02/1998

Microsynth Fabrics (I) Ltd – Silvassa

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Applications (IGNOU)

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Marathi